popcornvod.com 2017-11-08

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Statement explains our practices regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of certain information, including your personal information, by the Provider.

We recognize that your privacy is very important to you and that it is your right to control your personal information. We know that providing personal information is an act of trust and we take that trust seriously. We will never sell, rent or, except as set out in this Privacy Policy, otherwise disclose any of your personal information, including your Email address, to any third party without your consent. Unless you give us specific consent to act otherwise, the following policies will govern how we handles the personal information that you provide to us.

By your continued use of the Provider Services following the posting of this Privacy Policy (as applicable), you agree to this Privacy Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. This Privacy Policy forms part of and should be read in conjunction with our Terms of Use and any additional applicable terms.

  * In the course of using the Services, we ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you and administer your account ("Personal Information", “Personally Identifiable Information”). Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, your name, phone number, credit card or other billing information, email address and home and business postal addresses.
  * As you use the Services, our servers automatically record information that the browser sends whenever it points to a website or online service ("Log Data"). Log Data may include, but is not limited to, your computer's Internet Protocol address, browser type, the web page you were visiting before you came to one of the Sites and information you search for on a Site

  * Payment Information. We only use payment information, such as credit card numbers, as necessary for completing a particular transaction or fulfilling a service and to prevent abuse.
  * Other Information. We use the other information we collect from or about you in order to establish and enhance our relationship with you and to help deliver first-rate experience. Our use of this information includes the following general purposes: contacting you; customizing the content and advertising you view; fulfilling your requests for products or services; identifying content you share when you use the Provider Services; improving our services; conducting research; compiling aggregate data for internal and external business purposes; preventing potentially illegal activities; protecting our rights; other uses in accordance with our Terms of Use; and for any other purpose disclosed to you at the time we collect your information.
  * Promotional Communications. We may use your information to:

  * provide you with promotional information about our services, and other offerings that may be of interest to you;
  * provide information or offers to you that are related to our Services on behalf of ours business partners.

  * Recommendations and Advertising. We (and service providers acting on our behalf) may use information about you, including your use of our Services, to provide recommendations and advertisements on our Services and elsewhere on the web.

We are committed to protecting your personal information. We will not disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent except:

  * where we are required by law to disclose information to third parties;
  * where the disclosure is necessary for the performance of our operations (e.g. mail delivery, hosting services, protecting us from fraud, and payment of your account);
  * we buy or sell subsidiaries or business units. in connection with a corporate transaction, such as a sale, merger, consolidation or asset sale, or an internal reorganization, or in the unlikely event of an insolvency. If such a transaction or event required the transfer of customer information, then that information would be one of the transferred assets, but would remain subject to the commitments made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy or equivalent.

We also may share your personal information with third parties (i.e. agents or sub-contractors) specifically engaged by us to provide services to us, in which case we will require those parties to keep that information confidential and secure and to use it solely for the purpose of providing the specified services to us. 

We also provide analyses of our customers in the aggregate to prospective partners, advertisers, movie distributors and other third parties. We do this so that we and our business partners can understand you better, and so we can keep bringing you first-rate services. We may also disclose, on an anonymous basis, literal statements made by our customers. At no time, however, will we disclose personal information about specific customers. 

Linked websites are not under our control and we are not responsible for the conduct of companies linked to our Website. Before disclosing your personal information on any other website we advise you to examine its terms and use and privacy policy. 

Changing or Deleting Your Information All our members may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in their registration profile by logging into their account and changing the user preferences associated with their account. If you completely delete all such information, your account may be deactivated. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes.

What is a cookie?

  * Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information which are downloaded to your personal computer, mobile or other device when you visit a website. Cookies are then sent back to the originating website on each subsequent visit, or to another website that recognizes that cookie. Cookies are useful because they allow a website to recognize a user’s device.
  * Persistent cookies - these cookies remain on a user’s device for the period of time specified in the cookie. They are activated each time that the user visits the website that created that particular cookie.
  * Session cookies - these cookies allow website operators to link the actions of a user during a browser session. A browser session starts when a user opens the browser window and finishes when they close the browser window. Session cookies are created temporarily. Once you close the browser, all session cookies are deleted.
  * Cookies do lots of different jobs, like letting you navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences, and generally improve the user experience. They can also help to ensure that adverts you see online are more relevant to you and your interests.
  * You can find more information about cookies at [www.allaboutcookies.org](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://allaboutcookies.org/&sa=D&ust=1493892974815000&usg=AFQjCNFydxIYAaYrGXCATCO-t3zXbg37yw) and [http://youronlinechoices.eu](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://youronlinechoices.eu/&sa=D&ust=1493892974815000&usg=AFQjCNE8iuEZzn7a-M5VWhL3cd3DrsKS6A)

Cookies used on the Website A list of all the cookies that can be used on the Website by category is set out below.

  * Strictly necessary cookies - These cookies enable services you have specifically asked for. For those types of cookies that are strictly necessary, no consent is required. These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the Website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the Website. Without these cookies services you have asked for, like shopping baskets or e-billing, cannot be provided.
  * Performance cookies - These cookies collect anonymous information on the pages visited. By using the Website, you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your device. These cookies collect information about how visitors use the Website, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. It is only used to improve how the Website works.
  * Functionality cookies - These cookies remember choices you make to improve your experience. By using the Website, you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your device. These cookies allow the Website to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more personal features. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customize. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. The information these cookies collect may be anonymized and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.
  * Targeting or advertising cookies - These cookies collect information about your browsing habits in order to make advertising relevant to you and your interests. 
  * These cookies are used to deliver adverts more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. They are usually placed by advertising networks with our permission. They remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organizations such as advertisers. Quite often targeting or advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organization.

A guide to behavioral advertising and online privacy has been produced by the internet advertising industry which can be found at www.youronlinechoices.eu. The guide contains an explanation of the IAB’s self-regulatory scheme to allow you greater control of the advertising you see. 

Using browser settings to manage cookies

  * The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether. You can also disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the website of its manufacturer.
  * However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of the Website’s essential features, we recommend you leave them turned on. For example, if you block or otherwise reject cookies you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Basket, proceed to Checkout, or use any of our products and services that require you to Sign in. If you leave cookies turned on, remember to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.

We may periodically make changes to this Privacy Policy and will notify you of these changes by posting the modified terms on the Website. We recommend that you revisit this Privacy Policy regularly. If we are going to use Personal Information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you by posting a notice on our Services. You may determine when this Privacy Policy was last updated by referring to the date found at the top of the first page of this Privacy Policy "This Privacy Policy was last modified and is effective as of”.

We/Us refers to:   
with registered office in:           

If You wish to contact  in relation to the Website You can do so by e-mailing Us to support@popcornvod.com
